Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. Brouillard Communications Vertical Files, 1931-2002 and undated RL.11021
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Companies, 2
  - DuPont, 1968-1996; (4 folders) (Box 40)
  - Dutch PTT, 1989-1991; (2 folders) (Box 40)
  - Eastern Air Lines, 1986-1990 (Box 40)
  - Eaton, 1977-1991 (Box 40)
  - Economist, 1991 (Box 40)
  - Edison Electric Institute/Association of Electric Companies, 1989-1997 (Box 40)
  - EDS, 1991 (Box 41)
  - Eli Lilly, 1989-1995 (Box 41)
  - EMCOR, 1982 (Box 41)
  - Emerson, 1989-1994 (Box 41)
  - Emhart, 1988 (Box 41)
  - Engelhard, 1980-1983 (Box 41)
  - EniChem, 1987 (Box 41)
  - Enron, 1979-1998 (Box 41)
  - Entergy, 1990 (Box 41)
  - Eosat, 1989 (Box 41)
  - Epsom, 1985 (Box 41)
  - Equant, 1998 (Box 41)
  - Equitable/AXA, 1934-1999 (Box 41)
  - Ericsson, 1983-1987 (Box 41)
  - Ernst & Young, 1987-1999 (Box 41)
  - Esmark, 1974-1981 (Box 41)
  - Ethyl, 1987-1990; (2 folders) (Box 41)
  - Everex, 1989 (Box 42)
  - Ex-Cell-O, 1985 (Box 42)
  - Exide, 1991 (Box 42)
  - Experian, 1990s (Box 42)
  - Exxon, 1969-1999 (Box 42)
  - Fairchild, 1990-1991 (Box 42)
  - Falcon Jet, 1992 (Box 42)
  - Falconbridge, 1975-1981 (Box 42)
  - Fannie Mae, 1984-1990 (Box 42)
  - Fansteel, 1986-1991 (Box 42)
  - Farley Industries, 1987 (Box 42)
  - Federal Express, 1989 (Box 42)
  - Federal Mogul, 1991 (Box 42)
  - FFV (Sweden), 1987 (Box 42)
  - FGIC, 1991 (Box 42)
  - Fiat, 1989 (Box 42)
  - Fiatallis, 1984 (Box 42)
  - Fiber Industries, 1988 (Box 42)
  - Fidelity Investments, 1986-1989 (Box 42)
  - Figgie International, 1986-1989 (Box 42)
  - Financial Corporation of America, 1982 (Box 42)
  - Financial Times, 1984-1989 (Box 42)
  - Fireman's Fund, 1988 (Box 42)
  - Firestone, 1984 (Box 42)
  - First Boston, 1985-1991 (Box 42)
  - First Brands, 1986-1989 (Box 42)
  - First Chicago, 1985-1990 (Box 42)
  - First Fidelity, 1989-1990 (Box 42)
  - First Interstate Bank, 1985 (Box 43)
  - First Investors, 1985-1987 (Box 43)
  - Fisher, 1943 (Box 43)
  - Fleet Bank, 1995 (Box 43)
  - Fleet Financial, 1981-1997 (Box 43)
  - Flour Corporation, 1987 (Box 43)
  - FMC, 1964-1979 (Box 43)
  - Fokker, 1985-1988 (Box 43)
  - Ford, 1945-1991; (2 folders) (Box 43)
  - Fortis, 1995-1998 (Box 43)
  - Fortune Brands, 1997-1998 (Box 43)
  - Foster Wheeler, 1998 (Box 43)
  - Foxboro, 1984-1988 (Box 43)
  - Freddie Mac, 1997-2000 (Box 43)
  - Freeport McMoran, 1997 (Box 43)
  - Freightliner, 1983 (Box 43)
  - Frito-Lay, undated (Box 43)
  - Fruehauf, 1947 (Box 43)
  - Ft. Howard, 1984-1985 (Box 43)
  - Fujitsu, 1983-1997 (Box 43)
  - GAF, 1983 (Box 43)
  - GAMA (Gas Appliance Manufacturers Association), 1994-1996 (Box 43)
  - Gannett, 1981-1987 (Box 43)
  - Garrett, 1980-1983 (Box 43)
  - GenCorp, 1984-1985 (Box 43)
  - General Aviation, 1988 (Box 43)
  - General Dynamics, 1969-1990; (2 folders) (Box 44)
  - General Electric, 1943-1991; (4 folders) (Box 44)
  - General Electric Aircraft, 1989-1990 (Box 44)
  - General Electric Credit, 1985-1989 (Box 44)
  - General Foods, 1975-1984 (Box 44)
  - General Mills, 1985-1988; (2 folders) (Box 44)
  - General Motors, 1947-1991 (Box 45)
  - General Re, 1986 (Box 45)
  - Genicom, 1988 (Box 45)
  - Georgia-Pacific, 1983-1992; (2 folders) (Box 45)
  - Gerber, 1981 (Box 45)
  - Getty Oil, 1982-1984 (Box 45)
  - Giorgio Armani, 1990 (Box 45)
  - GK Technologies, 1980-1982 (Box 45)
  - Glass Container Manufacturers Institute, undated (Box 45)
  - Glaxo, 1989-1997 (Box 45)
  - Glendale Federal Bank, 1990 (Box 45)
  - Glidden, 1951 (Box 45)
  - Gloria Sachs, 1991 (Box 45)
  - Goldman Sachs, 1990 (Box 45)
  - Goldome, 1988 (Box 45)
  - Goodrich, 1988-1989 (Box 45)
  - Goodyear, 1977-1986 (Box 45)
  - Gordon Capital, 1990 (Box 46)
  - Gordon Holmes, 1990 (Box 46)
  - Gould, 1974-1987 (Box 46)
  - GPT, 1989-1990 (Box 46)
  - Grace (W.R.), 1979-1989 (Box 46)
  - Grainger, 1988 (Box 46)
  - Grand Metropolitan, 1988 (Box 46)
  - GRE America, 1989 (Box 46)
  - Great Northern Nekoosa, 1977-1989 (Box 46)
  - Great Western, 1987 (Box 46)
  - Greyhound, 1972-1990 (Box 46)
  - Groupe Schneider, 1996 (Box 46)
  - Grow Group, 1982-1985 (Box 46)
  - GTE, 1975-1998; (5 folders) (Box 47)
  - Guardian, 1990-1993 (Box 47)
  - Gulf & Western, 1982-1986 (Box 47)
  - Gulf Oil, 1957-1983 (Box 47)
  - Gulfstream Aerospace, 1983-1997 (Box 47)
  - Gypsum Domter, 1990 (Box 47)
  - Hall, Frank, 1988 (Box 47)
  - Hanson Trust, 1987-1994 (Box 47)
  - Harris, 1984-1994 (Box 47)
  - Hartford, 1997-1999 (Box 47)
  - HBO, 1987 (Box 47)
  - HCA (Hospital Corporation of America), 1986 (Box 47)
  - Health America, 1983-1985; (2 folders) (Box 47)
  - Hearst, 1987 (Box 48)
  - Heinz, 1987 (Box 48)
  - Hemar, 1984 (Box 48)
  - Henkel, 1983-1988 (Box 48)
  - Henley, 1986-1989 (Box 48)
  - Hercules, 1987-1989 (Box 48)
  - Herman Miller, 1985 (Box 48)
  - Hertz, 1988-1991 (Box 48)
  - Heublein, 1981-1982 (Box 48)
  - Hewlett Packard, 1986-1991; (2 folders) (Box 48)
  - Hilton International, 1988 (Box 48)
  - Hitachi, 1984-1991; (2 folders) (Box 48)
  - H.M. Government, 1990 (Box 48)
  - Hoechst Celanese, 1986-1989 (Box 48)
  - Hoechst Celanese, 1986-1989; (2 folders) (Box 49)
  - Hoffman LaRoche, 1992; (2 folders) (Box 49)
  - Holiday, 1985 (Box 49)
  - Honda, 1990-1991 (Box 49)
  - Honeywell, 1973-1998; (3 folders) (Box 49)
  - Hoover, 1930s (Box 49)
  - Houlihan Lokey Howard & Zuklin, 1989 (Box 49)
  - Household International, 1983-1984 (Box 49)
  - Houston Natural Gas, 1985 (Box 49)
  - Hughes Aircraft, 1970-1990; (3 folders) (Box 50)
  - Humana, 1985-1986 (Box 50)
  - Hutton, E.F, 1982-1987 (Box 50)
  - Hyundai Heavy Industries, 1982-1991 (Box 50)
  - IBM, 1978-1995; (5 folders) (Box 50)
  - IBM, 1978-1995 (Box 51)
  - IBM Mexico, 1988 (Box 51)
  - IC Industries, 1986-1990 (Box 51)
  - ICI World Class, 1987-1990 (Box 51)
  - IDA Ireland, 1989 (Box 51)
  - IEEE, 1988-1993 (Box 51)
  - Illinois Central, 1989 (Box 51)
  - IMC Fertilizer, 1988 (Box 51)
  - Imcera, 1990 (Box 51)
  - Inco, 1953-1997 (Box 51)
  - Independent Insurance Agents, 1986-1988 (Box 51)
  - Informix, 1990 (Box 51)
  - Ingersoll Rand, 1978-1998 (Box 51)
  - Inland Steel, 1984 (Box 51)
  - Integrated Resources, 1985-1986 (Box 51)
  - Intel, 1985-1991 (Box 51)
  - Interlake, 1984-1985 (Box 51)
  - Intermedics, 1983 (Box 51)
  - International Gold, 1987 (Box 51)
  - International Paper, 1980-1997; (4 folders) (Box 51)
  - International Telecharge (ITI), undated (Box 51)
  - InterNorth, 1983 (Box 51)
  - Investment Company Institute (ICI), 1995 (Box 51)
  - Irish Tourist Board, 1991 (Box 52)
  - ITC (International Telesystems Corporation), 1990 (Box 52)
  - ITT (International Telephone and Telegraph; Includes Bankers Trust), 1968-1997; (7 folders) (Box 52)
  - ITT Hartford, 1996 (Box 52)
  - IU International, 1980-1984 (Box 52)
  - James River, 1990 (Box 53)
  - Janssen, 1989 (Box 53)
  - Japan Air Lines, undated (Box 53)
  - Jeep/Eagle, 1988 (Box 53)
  - Jefferson Smurfit, 1987 (Box 53)
  - JI Case (International Harvester), 1990 (Box 53)
  - John Hancock, 1990-1991 (Box 53)
  - Johnson & Higgins, 1985-1999 (Box 53)
  - Johnson & Johnson, 1990-1994 (Box 53)
  - Johnson Controls, 1983-1989 (Box 53)
  - Johnson Matthey, 1987 (Box 53)
  - JWT Enterprise/IBM (Hong Kong), 1991 (Box 53)
  - Kaiser Aluminum, 1947-1990 (Box 53)
  - Keene, 1978-1980 (Box 53)
  - Kellogg, 1983 (Box 53)
  - Kemper, 1987-1990 (Box 53)
  - Key Corporation, 1998 (Box 53)
  - Keyspan Energy, 1997 (Box 53)
  - Kidder Peabody, 1984-1988 (Box 53)
  - K-Mart, 1990 (Box 53)
  - Knight Ridder, 1986-1997 (Box 53)
  - Kodak, 1971-1991; (3 folders) (Box 53)
  - Komatsu, 1988-1990 (Box 53)
  - Kraft, 1984-1988 (Box 53)
  - Kroll Associates, 1991 (Box 53)
  - Krupp, 1982-1986 (Box 53)
  - Kubota, 1982-1991 (Box 53)
  - Lazer Industries, 1987 (Box 54)
  - Lear Siegler, 1981 (Box 54)
  - Leaseway, 1984-1988 (Box 54)
  - Lederle, 1983-1985 (Box 54)
  - Lehman Brothers (Shearson Lehman), 1983-1991 (Box 54)
  - Leica, 1990 (Box 54)
  - LG Electronics, 1996 (Box 54)
  - Libbey-Owens-Ford, undated (Box 54)
  - Liberty Mutual, 1991-1997 (Box 54)
  - Lifesavers, 1981 (Box 54)
  - Liggett Group, 1976-1979 (Box 54)
  - Lightnet, 1984-1987 (Box 54)
  - Lilco (Long Island Lighting), 1986 (Box 54)
  - Linde, circa 1984 (Box 54)
  - Litton, 1982-1996 (Box 54)
  - Lockheed, 1981-1999; (3 folders) (Box 54)
  - Lomas Financial, 1988 (Box 54)
  - Lonestar Industries, 1980-1985 (Box 54)
  - Longines, 1930s (Box 54)
  - Loral, undated (Box 54)
  - Lotus, 1989-1991 (Box 54)
  - Louisiana Pacific, 1990 (Box 54)
  - LTV Aerospace, 1968-1986 (Box 54)
  - LTV Aerospace, 1968-1986 (Box 55)
  - Lucas, 1990 (Box 55)
  - Lucky Goldstar, 1988-1996 (Box 55)
  - Mack Trucks, 1983 (Box 55)
  - Macy's, 1983 (Box 55)
  - MagneTek, 1986-1988 (Box 55)
  - Mannesmann, 1986-2000 (Box 55)
  - Manufacturers Hanover, 1974-1990 (Box 55)
  - Manville, 1976-1988 (Box 55)
  - Marconi, 2000 (Box 55)
  - Marsh & McLennan, 1992-1999 (Box 55)
  - Martin Marietta, 1979-1995 (Box 55)
  - Massachusetts Mutual, 1985-1994 (Box 55)
  - Matsushita Electronics (Panasonic), 1983-1989 (Box 55)
  - Maxell, 1991 (Box 55)
  - Maxus, 1987 (Box 55)
  - Maytag, 1984 (Box 55)
  - Mazda, 1984-1985 (Box 55)
  - McCormick Dodge, 1985-1989 (Box 55)
  - McDermott, 1980-1985 (Box 55)
  - McDonald's, 1986 (Box 55)
  - McDonnell Douglas, 1982-1997; (3 folders) (Box 56)
  - McGraw-Hill, 1986-1996 (Box 56)
  - MCI, 1987-1997 (Box 56)
  - McKesson, 1985-1986 (Box 56)
  - Mead, 1981-1989 (Box 56)
  - Mellon Bank, 1983-1986 (Box 56)
  - Mercedes-Benz, 1990 (Box 56)
  - Mercer Management Consulting, 1995 (Box 56)
  - Merck, 1986-1997 (Box 56)
  - Meritor, 1986-1997 (Box 56)
  - Merrill Lynch, 1982-2000 (Box 56)
  - Metrahealth, 1995 (Box 56)
  - Metromedia, 1986 (Box 56)
  - Metropolitan Life Insurance, 1988-1999 (Box 56)
  - Micro-Pro, 1984 (Box 56)
  - Microsoft, 1990-1997 (Box 56)
  - MidCon, 1984 (Box 56)
  - Midlantic Bank, 1988-1992 (Box 56)
  - Millipore, 1985 (Box 57)
  - MiniScribe, 1988 (Box 57)
  - Miravant, 1996-1997 (Box 57)
  - Mita Copystar, 1990 (Box 57)
  - Mitel, 1986-1991 (Box 57)
  - Mitsubishi, 1984-1990 (Box 57)
  - Mitsui Group, 1990 (Box 57)
  - Mitsui Taiyo Kobe Bank, 1990-1991 (Box 57)
  - MNC Financial, 1987-1988 (Box 57)
  - Mobil, 1978-1998 (Box 57)
  - MoDo (Sweden), 1991 (Box 57)
  - Monsanto, 1971-1998; (3 folders) (Box 57)
  - Monsanto biotech, 1985-1988 (Box 57)
  - Monsanto Wear-Dated Carpet, 1991 (Box 57)
  - Montedison, 1990 (Box 57)
  - Moore McCormack, 1981-1985 (Box 57)
  - Morgan, J.P., 1988-1999 (Box 58)
  - Morgan Bank, 1986-1989 (Box 58)
  - Morgan Stanley, 1987-1991; (3 folders) (Box 58)
  - Morton Thiokol, 1984-1997 (Box 58)
  - Motorola, 1982-1997; (4 folders) (Box 58)
  - Motorola Codex, 1987-1988 (Box 58)
  - MSA, 1984-1986 (Box 59)
  - MTA, 1989 (Box 59)
  - Murata, 1987 (Box 59)
  - Mutual Broadcasting System, undated (Box 59)
  - Mutual of New York (MONY), 1990-1991 (Box 59)
  - NADA (National Automobile Dealers Association), 1990 (Box 59)
  - National Distillers, 1987-2001; (2 folders) (Box 59)
  - National Rifle Association (NRA), 1985-1989 (Box 59)
  - Nuclear Energy, 1998 (Box 59)
  - Pacific Gas & Electric (PG&E), 1990 (Box 59)
  - PacifiCorp, 1984-1989 (Box 59)
  - Pacific Telesis, 1985-1995 (Box 59)
  - Paine Webber, 1983-1998 (Box 59)
  - Pan American Coffee Bureau, 1962 (Box 59)
  - Pan American Satellite, 1988 (Box 59)
  - Pan American World Airlines (Pan Am), 1989-1991 (Box 59)
  - Panasonic, 1987-1991 (Box 59)
  - Panhandle Eastern, 1985-1986 (Box 59)
  - Parke Davis, 1947-1984 (Box 59)
  - Parker Hannifin, 1985-1991 (Box 59)
  - Paul Revere Life Insurance, undated (Box 59)
  - Peat Warwick (KPMG), 1988-1990; (2 folders) (Box 59)
  - Peat Warwick (KPMG), 1988-1998 (Box 60)
  - Pechiney (France), 1984 (Box 60)
  - Penn Central, 1982 (Box 60)
  - Pennant Systems, 1992 (Box 60)
  - Pennwalt, 1977-1986; (3 folders) (Box 60)
  - Pennzoil, 1987 (Box 60)
  - Pepsi-Cola, 1985-1987 (Box 60)
  - Perkin Elmer, 1989-1990 (Box 60)
  - Petromin (Saudi Arabia), undated (Box 60)
  - Pfizer, 1983-1996; (4 folders) (Box 60)
  - Pfizer, 1989-1996 (Box 61)
  - Pharmacia, 1996-1997 (Box 61)
  - Phelps Dodge, 1969-1982 (Box 61)
  - Phibro Energy, 1991 (Box 61)
  - Philip Morris, 1979-1997; (2 folders) (Box 61)
  - Philips, 1987-1996 (Box 61)
  - Phillips Petroleum, 1947-1991; (2 folders) (Box 61)
  - PHRMA (America's Pharmaceutical Research Companies), 1996-1999 (Box 61)
  - Pilkington, 1990 (Box 61)
  - Pillsbury, 1985-1988 (Box 61)
  - Pioneer Corporation, circa 1982 (Box 61)
  - Pirelli, 1986-1989 (Box 61)
  - Pitney-Bowes, 1985-1997 (Box 61)
  - Planned Parenthood, 1982-1990 (Box 61)
  - Plessey (Stromberg-Carlson), 1983 (Box 61)
  - PMA (Pharmaceutical Manufacturers Association), 1991; (3 folders) (Box 62)
  - Polar, 1991 (Box 62)
  - Potlatch, 1968-1977 (Box 62)
  - Port Authority of New York and New Jersey (Box 62)
  - Potomic Electric Power Company (Pepco), undated (Box 62)
  - Power companies, various, 1983-1989 (Box 62)
  - PPG Industries, 1977-1998; (2 folders) (Box 62)
  - Praxair, 1996 (Box 62)
  - Price Waterhouse, 1987-1999 (Box 62)
  - Prime Computer, 1985-1989 (Box 62)
  - Primerica, 1987-1989 (Box 62)
  - Principal Financial, 1985-1986 (Box 62)
  - Procter & Gamble, 1985 (Box 62)
  - Prudential, 1943-1991 (Box 62)
  - Prudential Bache, 1985-1989; (2 folders) (Box 63)
  - PTT Telecom, 1990-1991 (Box 63)
  - Pullman, 1943-1977 (Box 63)
  - Qantel, 1980-1981 (Box 63)
  - Quaker Oats, 1987 (Box 63)
  - Quantum Chemical, 1989-1990 (Box 63)
  - Questar, 1984 (Box 63)
  - Racal, 1989-1990 (Box 63)
  - Raymond Corporation, 1986 (Box 63)
  - Raytheon, 1991-1997 (Box 63)
  - RBOC (Regional Bell Companies), 1990 (Box 63)
  - RCA, 1946-1990 (Box 63)
  - Reader's Digest, 1990 (Box 63)
  - Reichhold, 1986 (Box 63)
  - Reliance, 1998 (Box 63)
  - Republic National Bank, 1989-1991 (Box 63)
  - Republic Steel, 1952 (Box 63)
  - Reuters, 1987-1991; (2 folders) (Box 63)
  - Reuters corporate, 1990-1996 (Box 63)
  - Reuters Corporate 2000, 1990 (Box 63)
  - Reynolds Aluminum, 1974-1988 (Box 64)
  - Rhone-Poulenc, 1987-1998 (Box 64)
  - Ricoh, 1996 (Box 64)
  - Ringler Associates, 1985 (Box 64)
  - RJR Nabisco, 1986-1991; (3 folders) (Box 64)
  - RJ Reynolds Tobacco, 1985-1986 (Box 64)
  - Robins, A.H., 1983 (Box 64)
  - Roche, 1988-1994 (Box 64)
  - Rockcor, 1985 (Box 64)
  - Rockwell International, 1979-1998; (4 folders) (Box 64)
  - Rohm & Haas, 1988 (Box 65)
  - Rolls-Royce, 1980-1991 (Box 65)
  - Rolm, 1989-1990 (Box 65)
  - Rombouts, 1990 (Box 65)
  - Royal, 1981 (Box 65)
  - Royal Canadian Mint, 1990 (Box 65)
  - R.R. (Railroads misc.), 1984-1985 (Box 65)
  - RTZ, 1990-1991 (Box 65)
  - Russ Togs, 1988-1989 (Box 65)
  - Ryder, 1987-1998 (Box 65)
  - Sabic, 1984-1990 (Box 65)
  - Safety-Kleen, 1988 (Box 65)
  - Saipem, 1986-1987 (Box 65)
  - SallieMae, circa 1996 (Box 65)
  - Salomon Brothers, 1990-1998 (Box 65)
  - Samsung, 1988-1991 (Box 65)
  - Sandoz, 1990-1991 (Box 65)
  - Santa Fe Industries, 1943-1983 (Box 65)
  - Sanwa Bank, 1988-1991 (Box 65)
  - Sara Lee, 1985-1991 (Box 65)
  - SAS Airline, 1991 (Box 65)
  - Saturn, 1990 (Box 65)
  - Savin, 1981-1983 (Box 65)
  - Scana Corporation, 1990 (Box 65)
  - Schering Drug, 1984 (Box 65)
  - Schering-Plough, 1985 (Box 65)
  - Schlumberger, 1987-1998 (Box 65)
  - Schott, 1985-1991 (Box 65)
  - Schwab, Charles, 1995-1997 (Box 65)
  - Schwinn, 1988 (Box 65)
  - Scripps Howard, 1985 (Box 65)
  - Seagram, 1973-1985 (Box 65)
  - Sea-Land, 1985 (Box 65)
  - Sears, 1982-1989 (Box 65)
  - Security Pacific, 1990 (Box 65)
  - Seligman, J.W., 1990 (Box 65)
  - Seven-Up (7-Up), 1983 (Box 65)
  - SFENA (France), 1986 (Box 65)
  - Sharp, 1988-1992; (4 folders) (Box 66)
  - Shawmut, 1987-1988 (Box 66)
  - Shaw Ross, 1991-1992 (Box 66)
  - Shearson/American Express, 1984 (Box 66)
  - Shell Oil, 1977-2002; (3 folders) (Box 67)
  - Shipbuilding, various, undated (Box 67)
  - Short Brothers, 1990 (Box 67)
  - Shuwa, 1987 (Box 67)
  - Siebel, 2000 (Box 67)
  - Siemens, 1988-1998; (2 folders) (Box 67)
  - Sierra Club, 1997 (Box 67)
  - Signal, 1984-1985 (Box 67)
  - Signode, 1985 (Box 67)
  - Singapore Telecom, undated (Box 67)
  - Singer, 1976-1986; (3 folders) (Box 67)
  - Skandia, 1988-1989 (Box 67)
  - SKF, 1985-1990 (Box 67)
  - Smith Barney, 1989-1997 (Box 67)
  - SmithKline, 1980-1989 (Box 67)
  - Smithsonian, 1984-1990; (5 folders) (Box 68)
  - SNET (Southwestern New England Telephone), 1983-1991 (Box 68)
  - Software companies various, 1985-2000 (Box 68)
  - Sonat, 1982-1985 (Box 68)
  - Sony, 1991-1992 (Box 68)
  - Sotheby's, 1990 (Box 68)
  - Southern Company, 1996-1998 (Box 68)
  - Southern Pacific, 1983 (Box 68)
  - Southwestern Bell, 1987-1990 (Box 68)
  - Sperry, 1979-1986 (Box 69)
  - Sprint/Telenet, 1987-1988 (Box 69)
  - Square D, 1989 (Box 69)
  - Squibb, 1934-1989; (2 folders) (Box 69)
  - Ssangyong, 1990 (Box 69)
  - St. Francis Hospital, 1992 (Box 69)
  - St. Joe Lead, 1976-1981 (Box 69)
  - St. Regis, 1974-1982 (Box 69)
  - Standard and Poor, 1990 (Box 69)
  - Standard Oil, 1987 (Box 69)
  - Stanley, 1983-1997 (Box 69)
  - State Farm, 1953 (Box 69)
  - Steel Alliance, 1999 (Box 69)
  - Steelcase, 1988-1989 (Box 69)
  - Steinway & Sons, 1992 (Box 69)
  - Sterling Drug, 1986 (Box 69)
  - Stewart & Stevenson, 1987 (Box 69)
  - Stone Container, 1987 (Box 69)
  - Storage Tek, 1985-1997 (Box 69)
  - Stuart James, 1990 (Box 69)
  - Sturm, Ruger & Company, 1990 (Box 69)
  - Sumitomo, 1989-1990 (Box 69)
  - Sun America, 1990 (Box 69)
  - Sun Petroleum, 1981-1985 (Box 69)
  - Sunkyong, 1990-1991 (Box 69)
  - Sunshine, 1989 (Box 69)
  - Swardovski, 1990 (Box 69)
  - Tandon, 1982-1986 (Box 69)
  - Tandy,(Radio Shack), 1989-1998 (Box 69)
  - Taylor Woodrow, circa 1985 (Box 69)
  - Telephone companies, various, 1983-1990; (2 folders) (Box 69)
  - Temple Island, 1984 (Box 69)
  - Templeton, 1992-1996 (Box 69)
  - Tenneco, 1979-1995 (Box 69)
  - Tenneco, 1979-1995 (Box 70)
  - Texaco, 1980-1998 (Box 70)
  - Texas Air, 1989 (Box 70)
  - Texas Instruments, 1985-1991 (Box 70)
  - Textron, 1978-1995; (2 folders) (Box 70)
  - Thomson-CSF, 1986-1989 (Box 70)
  - Thorn EMI, 1985 (Box 70)
  - 3M, 1986-1990; (5 folders) (Box 70)
  - TI Group, 1990-1991 (Box 71)
  - TIAA CREF, 1995 (Box 71)
  - Time Warner, 1990 (Box 71)
  - Times Mirror, 1986 (Box 71)
  - Timken, 1984-1994 (Box 71)
  - Tobacco Institute, 1982-1983 (Box 71)
  - Todd Shipyards, 1983 (Box 71)
  - Torchmark, 1990 (Box 71)
  - Toshiba, 1985-1990 (Box 71)
  - Towers Perrin, 1995 (Box 71)
  - Toyota, 1986-1990 (Box 71)
  - Transamerica, 1982-1991 (Box 71)
  - Transco, 1985-1986 (Box 71)
  - Travelers, 1960-1997; (3 folders) (Box 71)
  - Tribune, 1988 (Box 71)
  - Trinova (Libbey-Owens), 1986-1989; (2 folders) (Box 71)
  - Trinova (Libbey-Owens), 1986-1989 (Box 72)
  - TRW, 1974-1999; (3 folders) (Box 72)
  - Turner Construction, 1985 (Box 72)
  - TV Answer, 1991-1992; (2 folders) (Box 72)
  - Twentieth-Century Fox, 1983 (Box 72)
  - Tyco, 1998-2000 (Box 72)
  - Tymshare, 1981-1983 (Box 72)
  - Tyson, 1990 (Box 72)
  - Unions, various, 1982-1987 (Box 72)
  - United Steelworkers of America, 1983-1986 (Box 72)
  - US Chamber of Commerce, 1990 (Box 72)
  - US Council for Energy Awareness (USCEA), 1990 (Box 72)
  - USITA (Independent Telephone Association), 1973-1974 (Box 72)
  - USLIFE, 1997 (Box 72)
  - Value Line, 1989-1998; (2 folders) (Box 73)
  - Van Kampen Merritt, 1986-1991 (Box 73)
  - Varig (Brazil), 1988-1991 (Box 73)
  - Veba, 1987-1998 (Box 73)
  - VEPCO (Virginia Electric and Power Company)/Dominion Resources, 1982-1984; (2 folders) (Box 73)
  - VF Corporation, 1985 (Box 73)
  - Volkswagen, 1985-1989 (Box 73)
  - Volvo, 1984-1990 (Box 73)
  - Wachovia, 1986 (Box 73)
  - Wall Street Journal, 1989 (Box 73)
  - Walt Disney, 1990-1991; (4 folders) (Box 73)
  - Wang, 1980-1990 (Box 74)
  - Warner & Swasey, 1941-1979; (2 folders) (Box 74)
  - Warner-Lambert, 1984-1990 (Box 74)
  - Washington National, 1981-1987 (Box 74)
  - Waste Management, 1994 (Box 74)
  - Wasau Insurance, 1990 (Box 74)
  - Western Electric, 1951-1983 (Box 74)
  - Western Union, 1985-1989; (2 folders) (Box 74)
  - Westin Hotels and Resorts, 1990 (Box 74)
  - Westinghouse, 1943-1991; (3 folders) (Box 74)
  - WestLB, 1991 (Box 75)
  - Westvaco, 1984-1992 (Box 75)
  - Wheelabrator Technologies, 1994 (Box 75)
  - Whirlpool, 1978-1984 (Box 75)
  - White Consolidated, 1980-1984 (Box 75)
  - Whitman (IC Industries), 1981-1989 (Box 75)
  - Wiley (John) & Sons, 1989 (Box 75)
  - Williams Company, 1980-1985 (Box 75)
  - Williams Network, 1998 (Box 75)
  - Witco, 1984-1987 (Box 75)
  - Woolworth, 1998 (Box 75)
  - Xerox, 1971-1991; (4 folders) (Box 75)
  - Xerox, 1971-1991; (2 folders) (Box 76)
  - Yamaichi, circa 1987 (Box 76)
  - Zenith, 1984-1991 (Box 76)
  - Zurich Insurance Group, 1995-1998 (Box 76)
- Oversize Materials, 3
  - Companies--Singer, undated (Box 77)
  - Industries--Insurance (Business Insurance magazine), 1995-1997; (2 folders) (Box 77)
  - Industries--Restaurants (Nation's Restaurant News), 1997 Jan. (Box 77)
- Audiovisual Materials, 4
  - RL11021-3/4-001. Telecommunications interviews tape 1 of 2. 1997. 3/4 videocassette. (Box 78)
  - RL11021-3/4-002. Telecommunications interviews tape 2 of 2. 1997. 3/4 videocassette. (Box 78)
  - RL11021-VHS-001. TV Answer: Opportunities for Advertisers and Programmers. Undated. VHS. (Box 78)
  - RL11021-VHS-002. Telecommunications interviews. 1997. VHS. (Box 78)
  - RL11021-CAS-001. Radio TV Reports. Circa 1991. Sabina Airlines 91R00125. :60; KLM 90R07558. :60; Lufthansa 90R48273. :60. Audiocassette. (Box 78)